https://www.ariseandshine.com/privacy-policy

Due to the current worldwide situation shipments to some countries are taking longer than expected.
We are currently experiencing email and phone service outages due to fire and power outages in Southern Oregon. We are receiving, processing and shipping orders from our Washington state warehouse. We will reply to emails and return phone calls as soon as we are able to retrieve your messages and other inquiries. Thank you for your patience. Be safe.
0
Home
About
About Arise & Shine
Arise & Shine Origins & History
Natural Concepts
Founder Richard Anderson, Honorary ND, NMD
All About Cleansing
Tote Bag
Our experienced Cleanse Support Staff is here to support you @360-841-7106 or support@ariseandshine.com
Resources
Recipes For Cleansers
View Recipe Ideas
Downloads
Cleanse Guide
Cleanse Daily Tracking - 28 Day
Cleanse Daily Tracking - 14 Day
Food Combining Chart
Ariseandshine.com Privacy Policy
Ariseandshine.com is a spam free zone. Arise & Shine will not use your information for any purpose, without your permission, except as set forth in this privacy policy.
Privacy policy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.ariseandshine.com
At Arise & Shine, we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.
We believe that promoting and strictly adhering to fair information practices build customers' trust and confidence using the Internet and helps to secure our future online.
This privacy policy discloses the following information:
What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through the web site
The organization collecting the information
How the information is used
With whom the information may be shared
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under control
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you feel that Arise & Shine is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please contact us by:
Email: admin@ariseandshine.com Phone: 360-930-6008 Postal Mail: PO Box 2845, Mount Vernon, Washington- USA
Your confidence that we abide by our privacy policy is very important to us.
Information Collection and Use
Arise & Shine is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.  We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. A&S collects information from our customers at several different points on our website.
Ordering
We request information from the customer on our order form. Here a customer must provide contact information (like name and address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers’ orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. Arise & Shine's website is secure and hackers can not access your private information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie while on our site will only be used to link to personally identifiable information at your request. For example, saving your personal details in a cookie when you place an order so you don't have to re-enter them the next time you visit the site. Cookies allow us to tailor our site to better match your interests and preferences. Most Internet browsers allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or require a warning before a cookie is stored. Please Note: Cookies must be enabled on this site or our shopping cart will not remember what has been added to it.
We may also automatically collect and store: technical information when you connect to our site that is not personally identifiable, such as name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet Protocol ("IP") address of the computer you are using, the browser software you are using, your operating system, and the time, date, and/or the Internet site from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information only as aggregate data to determine the number of visitors to various sections of our site, to ensure the site is working properly, and to help make our site more useful. We do not use it to track or record information about individuals.
Sharing
Arise & Shine uses a bank to process credit cards for customer orders. Our bank does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Links
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware, in the event that you choose to visit other sites via the links on our site, Arise & Shine is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our customers to be aware of when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from customers via surveys or contests.
Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the customer, therefore, has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code, or age level).
Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.
Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Contact or survey information may also be used for marketing purposes, but only if you give your express permission to do so via a checkbox on the survey or contest application form.
Special Offers
Existing customers may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, or a newsletter.  Out of respect for the privacy of our customers we present the option to not receive these types of communications.  Please see our choice and opt-out option below.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If your personal information changes (such as your postcode), or if you wish to be removed from our database, you can correct, update or remove your personal data by sending an email to: admin@ariseandshine.com
Choice/Opt-out
Our customers are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to filling their order at the point where we ask for the information. Our order form has an opt-out mechanism so customers who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. We also supply an unsubscribe option at the bottom of every e-mail that we send.
Customers who no longer wish to receive newsletters or promotional materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by emailing Arise & Shine at: admin@ariseandshine.com
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our customers are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify customers by way of an email. Customers will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
0
Home
About
About Arise & Shine
Arise & Shine Origins & History
Natural Concepts
Founder Richard Anderson, Honorary ND, NMD
All About Cleansing
Our experienced Cleanse Support Staff is here to support you @360-841-7106 or support@ariseandshine.com
